[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what country was the 2000 Academy Award winning movie Gladiator filed?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["England", "Morocco", "Malta"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many Earth masses is the Sun?", "correct_answer": "330,000 Earth masses", "incorrect_answers": ["395,000 Earth masses", "310,000 Earth masses", "275,000 Earth masses"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What contributed to the quick tipping over of the luxury ocean liner in the movie The Poseidon Adventure?", "correct_answer": "There was not enough ballast", "incorrect_answers": ["Shelley Winters was too close to the starboard side of the boat", "Not enough speed when the wall of water hit", "Engines were at full power too long so they shut down"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Mean Girls, Cadys family moved to Evanston, Illinois so Cadys mom could take on a new job. Where did Cady and her family use to live?", "correct_answer": "Africa, where her parents were anthropologists", "incorrect_answers": ["Los Angeles, where her parents were actors", "Rome, where her parents were theologians", "Australia, where her parents were aborigines"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the capital and largest city of Jamaica?", "correct_answer": "Kingston", "incorrect_answers": ["Montego Bay", "Kigali", "Harare"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Name the largest known species of ammonite, which was found in Germany in 1895.", "correct_answer": "Parapuzosia seppenradensis", "incorrect_answers": ["Allonautilus perforatus", "Nautilus pompilius", "Parapuzosia bradyi"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the hit movie Aliens, who/what did Privates Hudson and Vasquez discover, via motion tracker, on their initial sweep of the complex?", "correct_answer": "Hamster", "incorrect_answers": ["Hicks", "Newt", "Alien"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In chat jargon, the emoticon  [8-] refers to this person.", "correct_answer": "Frankenstein", "incorrect_answers": ["Elvis", "Ronald Regan", "The Pope"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these ingredients is not used in the preparation of the Chinese dish called Ants climbing a tree?", "correct_answer": "Fish", "incorrect_answers": ["Garlic", "Noodles", "Meat"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to legend, what year is the luckiest year to be born in?", "correct_answer": "the year of the dragon", "incorrect_answers": ["the year of the rooster", "the year of the boar", "the year of the dog"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What word refers to the art or science of making timepieces and measuring time?", "correct_answer": "horology", "incorrect_answers": ["timeology", "numerology", "periodology"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the classic movie High Society, what was the distinguished last name of the brides family?", "correct_answer": "Lord", "incorrect_answers": ["Cabot", "Rockerfeller", "Vanderbuilt"]}]